//List of Jeopardy questions and answers
const QA = [{
    //Category  1 - Cat breeds
    Num: 1,
    question: 'What is the most common hairless cat breed?',
    answer: 'sphinx'
}, {
    //Category 2 - Coat patterns
    Num: 2,
    question: 'What is the most common cat fur pattern?',
    answer: 'tabby'
}, {
    //Category 3 - Folklore and Superstition
    Num: 3,
    question: 'What colored cat is widely considered to be bad luck?',
    answer: 'black'
}, {
    //Category 4 - In pop culture
    Num: 4,
    question: 'This Internet cat is famous for wearing her famous unhappy facial expression.',
    answer: 'grumpy cat'
}, {
    //Category 5 - Wild and Big Cats
    Num: 5,
    question: 'The name of this cat species is Simba.',
    answer: 'lion'
}, {
    Num: 6,
    question: 'What is the largest cat breed?',
    answer: 'maine coon'
}, {
    Num: 7,
    question: 'What is another word used to describe a tri-colored cat?',
    answer: 'calico'
}, {
    Num: 8,
    question: 'How many lives does a cat have? (Enter a word.)',
    answer: 'nine'
}, {
    Num: 9,
    question: 'This famous cartoon cat chases a mouse he can never catch and eat.',
    answer: 'tom'
}, {
    Num: 10,
    question: 'The name of this wild cat species is a popular sportswear brand.',
    answer: 'puma'
}, {
    Num: 11,
    question: 'What domestic cat breed is a mix between domesticated cat breeds and the Asian Leopard cat?',
    answer: 'bengal'
}, {
    Num: 12,
    question: 'This fur pattern only occurs in female cats.',
    answer: 'calico'
}, {
    Num: 13,
    question: 'What job title did witches give cats?',
    answer: 'familiar'
}, {
    Num: 14,
    question: 'What rapper is also described as the MaryJane Loving Feline?',
    answer: 'dojacat'
}, {
    Num: 15,
    question: 'What is the smallest wild cat species?',
    answer: 'rusty spotted cat'
}, {
    Num: 16,
    question: 'What cat breed is famous for being cross-eyed?',
    answer: 'siamese'
}, {
    Num: 17,
    question: 'What part of a cats genetics controls their fur color/pattern?',
    answer: 'chromosomes'
}, {
    Num: 18,
    question: 'Followers of what religion admire cats for their cleanliness.',
    answer: 'islam'
}, {
    Num: 19,
    question: 'What cartoon cat loves Lasagna? ',
    answer: 'garfield'
}, {
    Num: 20,
    question: 'How many wild/big cat species can roar?',
    answer: '4'
}, {
    Num: 21,
    question: 'What cat breed is famous for having having eyes that are two different colors?',
    answer: 'khao manee'
}, {
    Num: 22,
    question: 'How many cat fur patterns are there?',
    answer: '6'
}, {
    Num: 23,
    question: 'What Egyptian goddess is represented by a cat?',
    answer: 'bastet'
}, {
    Num: 24,
    question: 'Who was the first feline animated film star?',
    answer: 'felix'
}, {
    Num: 25,
    question: 'What genus do Lions, Tigers, and other big cats belong too?',
    answer: 'panthera'
}
]